{
    "subject": "resource/Amr_Kashmiri",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Amr Kahmiri",
    "human_readable": "The name of Amr Kashmiri is Amr Kahmiri.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.840912401676178,
            "question": "What is the correct spelling of Amr Kashmiri's name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7396252751350403,
            "question": "Is there a discrepancy between how Amr Kashmiri's name is commonly known and its official spelling?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.733569860458374,
            "question": "Why might there be a difference in the spelling of Amr Kashmiri's name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7120592594146729,
            "question": "What is the difference between 'Amr Kashmiri' and 'Amr Kahmiri'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6738952994346619,
            "question": "How does Amr Kashmiri's name differ from its official spelling?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6673051118850708,
            "question": "If someone was searching for information about Amr Kashmiri, would they find accurate results using 'Amr Kahmiri'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.047871604561805725,
            "question": "Could this misspelling lead to confusion or inaccuracies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03752130642533302,
            "question": "What is the importance of using the correct spelling of a person's name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03228871151804924,
            "question": "Should we always strive to use the officially recognized spelling of names?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.012668767012655735,
            "question": "How can we ensure that information about individuals is accurate and reflects their true identities?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Amr Kashmiri is Amr Kahmiri.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2587_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Should we always strive to use the officially recognized spelling of names?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2587_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the importance of using the correct spelling of a person's name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2587_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could this misspelling lead to confusion or inaccuracies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2587_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2587_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2587_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2587_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2587_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2587_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2587_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2587_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2587_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2587_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2587_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents consistently refer to his name as \"Amr Kashmiri\". There's no mention of \"Amr Kahmiri\".  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this response is that the documents mention Amr Kashmiri's full name as \"Amr Saleem Kashmiri\" and his nickname/alternative name is not mentioned to be \"Amr Kahmiri\", but rather \"Amr kashmiri\" without a space between the two parts of the last name."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents consistently refer to the individual as \"Amr Kashmiri\" and not \"Amr Kahmiri,\" thus the statement \"The name of Amr Kashmiri is Amr Kahmiri\" is incorrect based on the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}